My name is Dru Knox.
I'm the Head of Product & Design at Tessl.
I'll be giving a webinar on the Agent Context Development Lifecycle
with DevOps legend Patrick Debois on February 26th at 4 p.m.
London time.
The talk goes over standard developer
tooling concepts like CI/CD, unit and integration
testing and analytics, and maps those to context engineering
to help you create more predictability and reliability in your agent work.
The talk is great for any devs who are deep in agents
and want to find a way to make their work more rigorous and scale to their teams,
or anyone who's new to agents and looking to get started
in context engineering with an opinionated context framework.
The webinar is free to attend.
Click the link below to register and I'll see you there